- 吸血鬼后裔  前情回顾  - 怪物回来了
- Previously on Legacies... - The monsters are back.
我不知道该怎么办或者它会不会停止
I have no idea how or why  or if it's gonna stop.
这是我唯一的办法
This was the only way I could think of
让你看到
to get you to see
塞巴斯提安并不存在
Sebastian's not real!
闭嘴
Shut up!
你对我来说才不存在
You don't exist to me.
你对伊丽莎白说了什么
What did you say to Elizabeth?
塞巴斯提安
Sebastian?
- 躲开  - 我知道你说自己没事
- Go long! - Look, I know you say you're fine,
但你已经困在狼身很久了
but you were stuck as a wolf for a pretty long time.
- 是啊  我现在回来了  - 多亏了霍普
- Yeah, and I'm back now. - Thanks to Hope.
全世界都忘了我的存在
And the entire world  has forgotten that I exist.
我爱的男孩已经爱上了别人
And the boy I love has moved on.
还不行  但快了
Not yet, but soon.
我好像用很多的黑魔法伤了她
I kind of blasted Lizzie with enough
把魔鬼从她脑子里面驱赶出来
black magic to exorcise  an army out of her head.
霍普  安德里亚
Hope... Andrea...
迈克尔森
Mikaelson.
- 什么  - 已经确定了
- What? - It's official.
我都想起来了
I remember everything.
当我从乔西给我施的咒中醒来时
When I woke up from that spell Josie blasted me with,
你突然闪现在我脑中  就像中了迷魂药一样
you popped into my messed-up brain like an acid flashback.
怎么会  你算是这个世界上
How?  You are literally the only person
- 唯一知道我存在的人  - 损友世纪大团聚
- on the planet who knows that I exist. Epic former
必须要先等等了
frenemy reunion is gonna have to wait.
我们还有要紧事
We have bigger drama.
乔西和兰登今晚就要上床了
Josie and Landon are having sex tonight.
什么
What?
有个十周年舞会
There's a decade dance.
好吧  并不代表
Okay, well, that doesn't mean...
她让我找个借口
She asked me to find an excuse
和我爸在一起
to stay with my dad.
你一定要阻止他们
You have to stop it.
说出真相
Speak your truth.
把你的秘密和故事告诉他们
Spill your beans, tell your tale.
你怎么不告诉她
Why didn't you tell her?
因为我不去伤她的心
Because I didn't want to be the one to break her heart.
那是你的事
That's your job.
真不是时候
Ugh. Not a good time.
你到底是谁啊
Who the hell are you?
我是店主
I'm the Keeper.
这会比想象的容易得多
Ah. And this is gonna be a lot easier than I thought.
欢迎来到游戏
Welcome to the game.
还挺穿越的
Well, that was... anticlimactic.
我们要回学校保护兰登
We have to get to the school to protect Landon.
更像是保护乔西远离兰登
More like protect Josie from Landon by warning her
警告她将要和人型木偶上床了
she's about to have sex with a human-sized muppet.
刚才怎么回事
What just happened?
好像是游戏开始了
I think the game just started.
吸血鬼后裔
第2季   第5集
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
嘿
Hey.
- 嘿  - 怎么了
- Hey. - Oh! What?
干嘛啊
What?
你能看见他吗
Can you see him?
我看见的只有个
All I see is a dude
不懂规矩的家伙
who can't respect boundaries.
我都说了  没人能看见我的
I told you. No one else can see me.
- 你个家伙 - MG
- Boy! - MG.
翻 译  RossyGeng
你出现幻觉了
You're trippin'.
我知道  我知道
Well... I know. I know, I know.
但是丽兹  她见过这个新来的吸血鬼
But Lizzie-- she-she met this new vampire.
- 对  叫塞巴斯提安  - 没错
- Oh, yeah. Uh, Sebastian. - Yeah.
翻 译  Carousel
她满学校的讲他
She's been flapping her gums about him all over school.
他不是真的
He isn't real.
我以为丽兹
So I thought Lizzie was
翻 译  Pretender
看不见他了  但现在我能看见他了
losing it, but now I am seeing him.
所以  要么我出现幻觉了  要么这货
So, either I'm hallucinating, or this dude...
翻 译  晁安  兔兔秃了
搞什么
Whoa. What the...?
你能别碰我吗
Would you stop touching me?!
兄弟
buddy.
问问他想干嘛
ask him what he wants.
他想找回他的身体
He wants us to find his body.
他说他的身体被风干在某处的箱子了
He says he's been desiccated in a box somewhere.
特效：小螺号
他记不清细节了
He's a little vague on specifics.
我记不清
I am vague,
校 对   可爱马丁
是因为  如上所述
because, as aforementioned...
我被风干在
I am, uh, desiccated
特 效   麦 斯
箱子里了
in a box!
天呐  我是个和平主义者
Oh, my God. I'm a pacifist.
但如果你再碰我头发  我就动手了
But if you touch my hair again, we will throw hands.
好啊
Oh. Yeah. Yeah. Whoa.
住手
Stop!
抱歉
Sorry.
请告诉你那位比你聪明百倍的朋友
Please tell your far more intelligent friend
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
我最近与血有了联系
that I have recently come into contact with blood.
刚好够得到你狭隘的思维
Just a... just enough to reach that very limited mind of yours.
血液腐臭了
The blood was rancid.
你还记得我们搬走的那个恶心血泉吗
You remember that nasty blood fountain we moved?
好了  大家齐心协力
All right, everybody work together.
丽兹随时都能到
And Lizzie's gonna be here any second.
相信我  98只红气球肯定是不够的
And trust me, you do not want to have only 98 red balloons.
什么事这么好笑
What's so funny?
你说你和乔西爱得火热  是吧
You said you and Josie were getting pretty intense, right?
是啊
Yeah.
而且今晚有舞会
And it's a dance.
跳舞嘛  怎么了
It's a dance. So?
她觉得就是今晚了
She thinks it's gonna happen tonight.
不  不可能的
No, there's no way.
- 兄弟  舞会后上床太  - 太什么
- Dude, sex after a dance is so... - So, what?
80年代吗
Eighties?
我和丽兹说过了
So, I talked to Lizzie,
她今晚会和我爸待在镇上
and she's actually gonna stay in town with my dad tonight.
- 好吧  - 好的
- Good. - Yeah.
就是跟你说一下  是吧
Just an FYI, right?
是啊
Yeah.
兄弟
Dude.
我没事
I'm cool.
就是有点神经质
Just... just a little jumpy.
你最近一直很神经质啊
You've been a little jumpy a lot lately.
如果这事情太多了  你没必要
If all this stuff is too much, you don't have to...
暴露疗法  应该对我有好处
Exposure therapy. It's, uh... it's supposed to be good for me.
而且  我想参加今晚的舞会
Plus, I want to be able to handle the dance tonight.
是啊  万一霍普刚好
Yeah, in case Hope happens to accept
接受你的邀请了呢
the invitation you sent her?
晚上担心担心你自己吧
Dude, how about you worry about yourself tonight?
我有的
I am.
好吧  咱们再试试
HOPE: Okay, let's try this again.
既然我们被困在这了  要不我们不聊聊
So, since we're trapped here, are we ever gonna talk about how
你是怎么从马里之洼回来的并且不告诉我们
you came back from Malivore and decided not to tell any of us?
抱歉  我正顾着不让咱俩被撞死
Sorry. I'm a little busy keeping us from being roadkill.
保护咒
Projectium Deflecta.
这样应该能保护我们
That should protect us.
我们在这没法用魔法了
I don't think we have magic here.
是你施错咒了吧
Or you just did the spell wrong.
你这样有什么用吗
How's that siphoning going?
好吧  显然是没有魔法
Okay, fine. There's obviously no magic.
我们在某种死亡迷宫里
And we're in some sort of death maze from hell.
还有
And...
为什么是80年代
Why is it the '80s?
说到
Speaking of...
你玩过青蛙过街吗
Have you ever played Frogger?
酸洗牛仔裤真适合你
Acid wash is clearly your thing.
是吗  你也很狂野嘛
Right? You kind of look fierce, too.
谢谢
Thank you.
但现在我们的离开这
But now we got to get out of here.
我的头发还湿着
Oh. My hair is still wet.
就该料到如此的
Should have seen that one coming.
乔西  我能给舞池提个意见吗
Josie, may I make a suggestion about the dance floor?
你不是应该
Aren't you supposed to be having
- 在和你爸吃早午餐吗  - 爸爸
- brunch with your father? - Dad.
我很抱歉  萨尔茨曼校长
Hey, I'm sorry. Uh... Principal Saltzman.
我恐怕必须提醒你
I'm afraid I must remind you
法庭命令你
that you are prohibited from being here.
不能来这的
By court order.
别紧张  范布尔多
Relax, Fumbledore.
我和警长说明此事了
I cleared it with the sheriff.
我是作为父亲身份来的
I'm here as a concerned parent, as
因为我的两个女儿最近经历了创伤性的事件
both my daughters recently experienced a traumatic event.
武士和鬼怪吗
The samurai and the Oni Demon?
乔西都跟我说了
Josie told me all about it.
我没事  谢谢你来看我
I'm okay. Thank you for checking in, but
但一切都好
everything's fine.
好吧
All right.
那丽兹呢
But what about Lizzie?
她也见不着影
She was a no-show, too.
她去哪了
So, where is she?
她说有事要办
She said she had an errand to run.
好吧
All right.
她回来之前我哪都不去
Well, I'm not going anywhere until she gets back
我知道她也没事
and I know that she's okay, too.
我们还从没闯这么远
We've never made it this far.
地雷  不是吧
A land mine? Really?
这十年里发生了什么
What's wrong with this decade?
里根经济学  休闲可卡因吗
Reaganomics? Recreational cocaine?
- 困在这里了吗  - 要是有解密方法或者
Jams? If only there was a secret
线索就好了
or-or a clue.
除非你能在这附近找到线索商店  霍普
Unless you see a clue store around here, Hope,
线索商店
那我不认为
then I don't think...
好吧
Okay.
失物招领处
在找什么吗
Looking for something?
对  我们怎么离开这儿
Yeah. How do we get out of here?
我们为什么在我们祖父母的年代里
And why are we in our grandparents' decade?
抱歉  我只熟悉这个时代
Oh, yeah. Sorry. It's the only decade I know.
结果证明是当穿着一身黑衣的人
Turns out you miss a lot of pop culture
把你们扔进一个巨大的泥坑里时
when guys in black suits drop you
会错过很多流行文化
into a giant pit of goo.
至于离开这里  你们别想了
As for getting out of here goes, uh, you don't.
这个游戏直到我的宠物吃了你们  然后你们死去
You play the game until my pet feeds on you, and then you die.
真正意义上的死亡
For reals.
这个游戏是专门为了杀死
This game was specifically designed
美少女而设计的  所以
to kill beautiful maidens, so,
我得说这是为你们量身打造的
I'd say it's a pretty good fit.
真高兴我们进来了
Oh. So glad we stopped in.
我们走
Let's go.
还有
There is, um...
一个出去的方法
one... way out.
你们其中一人同意代替我的位置
One of you agrees to take my place.
听着  我也曾被困在这里  好吗
Look, I was trapped here once, too, okay?
就像你们俩  而且我
Just like you two, and I...
我真的不想永远在
I don't really feel like being
这里为游戏看门护院的
the Keeper of the Game, like, forever.
所以  你们其中一个
So, one of you agrees
同意戴上这个手镯  你们就可以
to wear this bracelet, you get to be
代替我了
the new me.
而另一人会被释放
And the other one is set free.
谢谢  但  不用
Thanks, but, uh, no thanks.
事实上  恐怕没有别的选择了
Actually, I'm afraid there's no other option.
没错
Yeah.
你们要么接受交易  要么我的宠物会杀了你们
You take the deal, or my pet kills you.
这就是游戏结局
That's the endgame.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
说曹操曹操到
Speak of the devil.
我好喜欢这个环节
Ah. I love this part.
我的天
Oh, my God!
快跑  快点
Hurry, come on!
好吧  我想我们甩掉他了
Okay, I think we lost him.
至少我们终于逃出了那个破烂的
LIZZIE: At least we finally made it out
城镇广场  你可没帮上忙
of the lame town square, no thanks to you,
有些人差点又踩到地雷上了
Captain Almost-Stepped-on-the- Land-Mine-Again.
你用吹风机杀了我们
You killed us with a hair dryer.
我永远都不会忘记
Never forget.
学校在这边
The school's up this way.
要是路上有什么可谈就好了
If only there were something to talk about on the way.
一些急待解决的问题
Some burning question.
一些需要解释的神秘选择
Some mysterious choice that demanded an explanation.
好吧
Okay, fine.
我本来要告诉大家我回来了
I was gonna tell everyone that I was back.
但后来我看到了兰登和乔西
But then I saw Landon and Josie.
还有他们过得有多幸福
And how happy they were.
好像没有我  你们会过得更好
It just seemed like you all were better off without me.
你怎么回事
What is wrong with you?
你真有那么多殉道者情结
Do you really have that much of a martyr complex
你就不能  我不知道该怎么说
that you couldn't just-- oh, I don't know--
随便问问我们的感受吗
ask one of us how we were doing?
我知道这看起来有点
Look, I know that it seems kind of...
愚蠢  自私吗
Dumb? Selfish?
控制欲强吗
Controlling?
很痛苦
Painful.
没有了你  大家不会过的更好
No one's been better off without you.
兰登和乔西只是为填补你
Landon and Josie are just filling a void
和佩内洛普留下的空白
left by you and Penelope.
我爸爸很孤独
My dad is lonely.
拉斐尔又是一团糟  显然我
Raf's a mess again, and apparently
对男朋友们产生了幻觉
I'm hallucinating boyfriends.
如果我破碎的心灵还能记得你
If my broken mind can remember you,
那么也许乔西念的那个咒语
then maybe that spell Josie did
能让每个人都重拾记忆
could bring everyone's memories back.
你和兰登是天生一对
You and Landon are made for each other,
所以你得在他们在上床
which is why you need to tell him
之前告诉他和乔西
and Josie before they do the deed.
你幻想出了一个男朋友吗
You hallucinated a boyfriend?
一会告诉你
Tell you in a second.
对  他是真的  好
Yeah, he's real, all right...
但  该死的
but damn.
这家伙闻起来比那血泉还难闻
Dude smells worse than that blood fountain. Mm-hmm.
你们俩就是懦夫
SEBASTIAN: Oh, you're both weaklings.
闭嘴  你的脸看起来像牛肉干儿
Shut up. Your face look like beef jerky.
他在这吗
KALEB: Oh, is he here?
让他跟我谈谈
Tell him to talk to me.
虽然我很想那样
Oh, as much as I would love that,
在我衰弱的状态下  我只能在意志脆弱的人
in my diminished state, I can only appear
面前显现  就像你这样的
to the fragile-minded... like you.
他  说你
Um, he... says
必须和他有相同的
that you have to be on, like,
精神波动
the same spiritual wavelength.
这太疯狂了
SEBASTIAN: Oh, this is maddening.
你们两个大头菜给我的
The rancid blood that you two turnips
腐臭的血是不够的
bumbled on me was inadequate.
但只要有足够的新鲜血液  我一定会恢复
But with enough fresh blood, I will surely be restored.
对啊  我们不可能这么做
Yeah. No way we're doing that.
做什么
Doing what?
要是我能给你们想要的呢
Not even if I can give you what you want?
伊丽莎白·萨尔茨曼属于你一个人
Elizabeth Saltzman all to yourself.
没人会跟你争
Without my competition.
拜托  MG  他在说什么
Come on, MG, what's he saying?
等等
Hold on.
他还没说到重点部分
He's just getting to the good part.
让我自由  密尔顿
Set me free, Milton,
我向你保证
and I give you my word,
我马上离开这个镇子
I will leave this town at once.
他要我们把他唤醒
He wants for us to wake him up.
安排
刮胡子
做节目清单
我知道我忘了什么
I know I'm forgetting something.
焦虑警报
Uh-oh. Angst alert.
兰登的日志
Landon's journaling.
实际上  威廉姆斯先生
Actually, Mr. Williams.
我能问你一个私人问题吗
can I ask you a personal question?
艾玛不再和我约会了
Emma and I aren't dating anymore.
好吧  没有
Okay? And, no.
我不知道她会不会回来
I don't know if she's coming back.
事实上  我
Actually, I was, um,
我想知道你是
I was actually wondering how
怎么准备的
you were ready to, um...
你知道的
you know, um...
发生性关系
have sex...
就像
f-for, like,
就像  你的第一次的时候
for, like, your first time.
你是说你的第一次吗
You mean your first time?
没错
Yeah.
这么说你和乔西是认真的了
So you and Josie are getting serious?
- 我真的不想把事情搞砸  - 明白了
I really don't want to mess this up. Gotcha.
好吧  坐下说  兰登
All right, why don't you take a seat, Landon.
我认为当你
Well, I think
找到你想要跟他进行那一步
that when you've found the right person
的正确的人的时候
that you want to take that step with...
你自然就知道了
you just kinda know.
就像一个表情  对吧
It's-it's, uh, it's like a look, right?
就是这个样子然后
It's this look and then...
你知道
...you know.
让我先理清楚
ALARIC:  Let me get this straight.
你不知道这只吸血鬼是谁
You don't know who this vampire is
也不知道他是怎么下去的
or how he got down there,
只知道他因为某种
just that he's been desiccated
未知的原因被风干了
for some unknown reason,
他想让你们俩把他唤醒
and he wants you two to wake him up.
是的
Um... yeah. Y-Yeah.
差不多  差不多这样
That about-- that about covers it.
除非我漏了点什么
Uh, unless I'm missing something
否则我会说  让他腐烂吧
I would say... let him rot.
我们根本不知道他在那里干什么
We don't even know what he's doing down there
我也不知道
in the first place. Neither do I,
但可以肯定地说  没人会因为干好事
but it's safe to say that no one is desiccated
而变成那样
for being too nice.
好吧  但这并不意味着他有罪
Okay, but that doesn't mean he's guilty.
即使他有
And even if he is,
什么样的罪能要他那么多时间
what crime equals that kind of time?
假设他屠杀了
ALARIC: Hypothetically,
几十个村庄
the slaughter of a couple dozen villages.
你咋啥也不说  MG
You're awfully quiet over there, MG.
我  在这件事上我倾向于卡莱布
I'm... I'm leaning Kaleb's way on this one.
在吸血鬼出现之前  没吸血鬼
Vamps before... non-vamps.
不是的
That's not...
我不再是这里的负责人了
I know I'm not in charge here anymore.
现在  如果你想要我的选票  我建议你
Now, if you want my vote, I say don't do anything
在了解这家伙之前什么都不要做
till you know more about this guy.
我尊重你  萨尔茨曼博士
I-I respect that, Dr. Saltzman,
但他说他会离开这里
but he said he'll leave town.
我们至少要给他一次机会让他信守诺言
We should at least give him a shot to keep his word.
我觉得我们应该像索尔兹曼博士说的那样守口如瓶
And I vote we hold tight like Dr. S. said.
我们得弄明白塞巴斯蒂安到底想要什么
We, we figure out what Sebastian really wants.
我们要怎么做
How are we gonna do that?
交给我吧
You leave that to me.
好吗
All right?
谢谢你的点子  兄弟
Thanks for the wisdom, man.
说实话  我还挺吃惊的你会想听我的建议
To be honest, I'm surprised you'd even want my opinion.
在你们投票让我出局之后
after you guys voted me out.
听着
Uh, look, uh...
在匿名投票中
confidential ballot and all...
我是唯一一个投票希望你留下的
I am the only one who voted for you to stay.
我知道你不想考虑这件事
I know you don't want  to think about this,
但是真实的世界是不会
but the real world isn't resetting
像这个东西一样会不停重置的
like this stupid one is,
也就是说  我们很快就能再次遇见
which means we are rapidly approaching
乔西的意外出现了  然后周而复始
Josie's unexpected journey there and back again.
捕熊陷阱
Bear trap.
我不会告诉他们我的存在
I'm not gonna tell them about be.
为什么呢
Ugh. Why not?
因为这也改变不了什么
Because it's not gonna change anything.
箭
Arrow.
抱歉
Sorry!
弗兰克  下次小心点
Be more careful next time, Frank.
那会改变所有的事
It would change everything.
不  不会的
No, it won't.
当我看见那个传送门的时候  我知道
When I saw that portal, I knew that there
只有一个办法阻止那些怪物进来
was only one way to stop the monsters from coming.
只要我跳回去  然后关上传送门就可以了
I'm just gonna have to jump back in and close it.
所有人都会再次彻底忘了我
Everyone's just gonna forget me all over again.
我的存在就是为了终结马里之洼的
I was created to be the loophole that ends Malivore.
这就是我存在的唯一原因
It's the only reason I exist.
这是我的命运
It's my destiny.
快跑
Run.
快点
Come on.
从这过去应该就是学校了
The school should be right through here.
准备好接受我的提议了吗
Ready to take that deal yet?
我准备接手那个迷宫  然后重新
I'm ready to take this maze and shove it up your...
迷宫  不  这不是个迷宫  这是个幻境
Maze? Oh, no, this isn't a maze. It's a labyrinth.
知道它们俩的区别吗
Know the difference?
我看起来很傻吗
Do I look like a nerd?
迷宫是多路径的  而幻境只有一条路径
A maze has multiple paths, a labyrinth only has one.
没错  就像我之前说的
Exactly. As I said before,
只有一个办法来终结它
there's only one way this is going to end.
我同意  她的腿很漂亮  但她绝对是个贱人
Granted, her legs are amazing, but she is a royal bitch.
我们该怎么做
What are we gonna do?
我们接受提议
We take the deal.
我留下来
And I stay behind.
必须得是我  我得去代替她
It has to be me. I'll take her place
这样你就可以被放出来了
and then you can be set free.
看见没  牺牲精神  霍普
See? Capital M-artyr complex, Hope.
牛头怪和守门人会一起过来  对吗
The Minotaur travels with the Keeper, right?
所以如果我留在最后  他们会被我困住
So if I stay behind, it'll be trapped with me.
既然每次只进来一个怪物
And since the monsters only come one at a time,
其它怪物就不会再跟着进来了
no other monsters ever will.
另外  没有人会知道我不在了
Besides, it's not like anyone's gonna know I'm gone.
除了你
Except you.
好时光  换个花样
* Good times for a change *
看看我的运气
* See, the luck I've had... *
不  我没看到丽兹
No, I haven't seen Lizzie.
她可能还在逛街买简·方达紧身裤呢
She's probably still out buying her Jane Fonda leotard.
所以  求你了  求你了
* So, please, please... *
你投了我一票希望我离开
You voted for me to leave.
就让我  就让我
* Let me, let me, let me *
就让我
* Let me... *
为什么
Why?
因为这是你想要的
Because it's what you wanted.
爸爸  你提出投票
Dad, you put it to a vote.
你知道这个地方不应该
You knew that this place shouldn't be run
再由一个人类来管理
by a human anymore,
你却不能自己主动提出离开
but you couldn't bring yourself to leave,
所以你让我们为你做了选择
so you had us make that choice for you.
这听起来好像你妈妈说的话
That sounds like something your mother would say.
她还说过  你的梦想就是创造一个
She also said that your dream was to create a place
我们可以学会做自己  有安全感的地方
where we could learn to be ourselves, to be safe.
你做到了
You've done that,
所以我们现在必须要继续下一个篇章了
so now we have to move on to the next chapter of our lives.
我们得学会没有你也能活下去
We have to learn to do this without you.
得到我想要的
* Get what I want... *
爸爸
Dad,
我投了你一票  这样你才能有自己的生活
I voted you out so you could have your own life.
开始约会
Start dating.
开始学会放手
Start letting us go,
因为我们都过的很好
because we're fine...
因为你
because of you.
穿那件吧
Definitely that one.
是吗
Yeah?
我给你也弄了一套衣服
I picked out an outfit for you, too.
吸血鬼先生  起床喜洋洋
Rise and shine, brother vampire.
像雨滴一样在我耳边低语
Talk to me like the rain,
我会躺下仔细听
and I will lie here and listen.
你是个诗人
You're a poet.
不是我  这是田纳西·威廉姆的诗  兄弟
Nah, that's Tennessee Williams, bruh.
但是告诉我我想听到的
But tell me what I want to hear,
还有它们是从哪里来的
and there's more where that came from.
你想知道些什么
What do you wish to know?
你是哪种吸血鬼
What kind of vamp you are.
是吸兔子血的还是人的
The kind that rips rabbits... or throats?
我只是
I am
一个做了错事的人
a man who has made mistakes,
但是如  如果你让我复活
but if-if you revive me,
我不会再犯错了
I will not make them again.
好极了
Great.
那我就不感兴趣了
Then I'm not interested.
这不就是你想听到的吗
Isn't that what you wanted to hear?
这个学校里已经有太多装腔作势的人了
You know, this school's already full of poseurs
否认他们的本能
denying their basic instincts.
我还希望你有所不同呢
I was hoping you were different.
看来没什么不一样
Guess not.
我因为你的罪变成了这样
I am in this state for the very sin that you desire.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
我以前吸了很多人的血
I fed on so many humans back in my day
不是因为饥饿  只是一个游戏而已
that it was no longer for hunger, it was merely sport.
鹅卵石都被血染红
The cobblestones, they ran red with blood.
既然这样
Well, in that case...
晚会结束后我就烧死你
...I'll burn you after the party.
你耍了我
You deceived me.
你看上去真美
you look amazing.
谢谢
Thank you.
你也是
So do you.
谢谢
Thank you.
你今天都干嘛了
What did you get up to today?
干点这个
little bit of this...
干点那个
little bit of that.
对不起
Oh. Sorry.
对不起  我  不  我才该说对不起
Sorry, I-- no, I'm sorry.
你呢
You?
一样
Same.
你还好吗
You okay?
- 你看起来好像  - 没事
- You seem... - Yeah.
我和我爸爸在一起来着
I was... with my dad.
现在没事了
It's fine now.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你好像  你看起来
You just... you seem...
- 有点不安  - 不  我只是
- fidgety. - No, no, I'm just, uh...
我只是太激动了
I'm just excited.
兰登
Landon.
你知道我们今晚不是非得
You know that we don't have to...
跳舞哈  如果你不想的话
dance tonight if you don't want to.
- 是吗  - 对啊
- Really? - Yeah.
那太好了
Okay, cool.
我们今晚也不一定非得做爱
We also totally don't have to have sex tonight.
除非  你所说的跳舞
Um... In case your use
是暗指别的
of dancing wasn't a metaphor.
- 的确  - 好吧
- It was. - Okay, good.
你很特别
You're special.
我希望这一刻也很特别
So I want it to be special.
那一刻我们凝视着彼此
That moment we both look at each other...
我们都了解
...and we both know.
听起来真美
That sounds nice.
让我们痛快的跳舞吧
Let's just enjoy the dance.
好的 舞池在那边
Yeah. Dance is that way.
- 我知道  - 好吧
- I knew that. - Right.
我说过
* I said *
亲爱的  让我们尽情的跳舞吧
* Dance hall days, love *
尽情的跳舞吧
* Dance hall days *
尽情的跳舞吧  我的爱
* Dance hall days, love *
握住她的手
* Take your baby by the wrist *
嘴里衔着紫水晶
* And in her mouth an amethyst *
嘿
Hey.
我弄清楚了
I figured it out.
说的就是塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian's an O.G.
冷血杀手
Cold-blooded killer.
- 真的吗  - 嗯
- For real? - Yeah.
我投票让他出局
And I voted to let him out.
我不这么想
I... I wasn't thinking.
你就是这么想的  好吧
Oh, you were thinking, all right.
涉及到丽兹·萨尔兹曼
About Lizzie Saltzman.
但这更证明了你追她的时候
But this is more proof that when you chase her,
你没做真实的自己  你明白吗
you're not peak MG, you know?
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do with that.
舞厅的日子
* Dance hall days... *
去跳舞排解一下吧
Dance it off.
DJ  气氛搞起来
DJ, hit me.
事情顺利得需要两个人
* It takes two to make a thing go right *
要让它消失也得需要两个人
* And it takes two to make it outta sight *
对  就这样  就这样
Yeah, all right, all right...
It Takes Two -  ROB BASE & DJ EZ ROCK
我现在就想摇滚
* I wanna rock right now *
我是罗伯·贝斯  我来到了这里
* I'm Rob Base and I came to get down *
我没有国际知名度
* I'm not internationally known *
但大家都知道我能玩转麦克风
* But I'm known to rock the microphone *
我很蠢笨  意味着非同寻常
* Because I get stupid, it means outrageous *
要想不被传染就远离我
* Stay away from me if you're contagious *
因为我是赢家
* 'Cause I'm the winner *
不  我不是失败者  我只是个MC
* No, I'm not a loser, to be an MC *
我要的是
* Is what I choose-a *
女人们爱我  女孩们为我疯狂
* Ladies love me, girls adore me *
我是说即使是那些从没见过我的人
* I mean even the ones who never saw me, like *
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
要开始疯狂起来了  准备好了吗
* I want you to get busy, you ready now? *
一  二  三  放松
* One, two, three, get loose now *
这需要两个人
* It takes two to make a *
这需要两个人  这  这
* It-it-it-it takes two to make a, it-it-it *
- 这需要两个人  - 我明白你为什么会觉得
- *It takes two. * - I get why you think
但是你得接受这笔交易
you need to take the deal, though.
我的存在也是为了一个原因
I exist for one reason, too:
与我姐姐结合
merge with my sister.
这就是我们的命对吧
That's our destiny, right?
除非
Unless...
我待在一个没有魔法的空间
I stayed here in a no-magic zone.
也许合体也不需要发生
Maybe the merge wouldn't have to happen,
乔西也就安全了
and Josie would be safe.
我是不会让我们永远待在这里的
There's no way I'm gonna let you do that.
我知道
I know.
但你也不是唯一一个烈士
But you're not the only one who can be a martyr.
我就知道你才是最明智的那一个
I knew you were the smart one.
那我们来处理这件事儿吧
Let's just get this over with. Oh!
别担心  当看守人也不错
Don't worry, it's not so bad being the Keeper.
也许有一天
And one day, maybe...
你会找到那个代替你坐这个位子的人
you'll find someone to take your place.
我不会那么做的
I would never do that. Aw...
我当时也对自己说了同样的话
I told myself the exact same thing.
小心点吧
Be careful with it.
这很脆弱
It's fragile.
如果它坏了
And if it breaks,
你就不再受人身牛头怪的保护了
you are not protected from the Minotaur anymore.
那我的朋友就可以出去了  是吧
And my friend gets out, right?
她就会从永恒痛苦的迷宫中
She is set free from the eternal pain
解脱出来  对没错
of the labyrinth, yes.
用词很小心嘛
That was very carefully worded.
她死了  好吧
She dies, okay?
就这个意思
That's what that means. Uh...
不妨这样想  她死  或者你们一起死
just think of it this way: either she dies or you both do.
这算是自我保护  小姐
It's self-preservation, kiddo.
- 你个婊子  - 你知道吗  当我第一次做这个交易的时候
- You're sick. - You know, when I first took this deal,
之前的看守人告诉我这整个迷宫
the previous Keeper told me that this entire labyrinth
是一个巫师几个世纪前建造的
was built by a sorcerer
目的是为了惩罚一个
centuries ago to punish a beautiful maiden
伤了他心的美丽女人
who refused his affections.
因为她不只是为了他而存在
Because she didn't exist just for him,
所以他惩罚她永远禁锢在此
he punished her forever.
但她逃了出来
But she got out.
她和另一个女人做了交易交换了位置
She traded places with another woman who came along,
然后那个女人困在了这里
who then trapped another woman,
以此往复
and so on and so forth.
我是说  你不能怪我们想离开这鬼地方的心
I mean, you can't really blame us for trying to escape,
你会吗
can you?
每个人都是为了自己
It's every woman for herself.
这就是这个游戏
That's the game.
我想现在没人是看守人了
I guess no one is the Keeper now.
我真希望你能和我们一样了解你的迷宫
I hope you know your maze as well as we do.
抱歉
Sorry.
幻境
"Labyrinth."
你看起来很有趣
* You look like you're lots of fun *
You Spin Me Round (Like a Record) - DEAD OR ALIVE
张开你爱的双臂
* Open up your lovin' arms *
小心  我来了
* Watch out, here I come *
你让我旋转  宝贝  旋转
* You spin me right round, baby, right round *
就像个唱片  宝贝  一圈
* Like a record, baby, right round *
一圈  一圈
* Round, round *
你让我旋转
* You spin me... *
哇哦
Whoa!
嘿  拉斐尔
Hey, Raf!
嘿  看来暴露疗法起作用了
Hey. Looks like exposure therapy worked.
看情况吧
Depends. Uh,
- 霍普来了吗  - 还没
- did Hope show up? - Not yet.
可能一会儿就来了吧
But she might show up still.
- 再等等  - 好
- Hang in there. Okay? - All right.
挺帅的
You look good.
一圈  一圈  一圈
* Right round, round, round. *
你从哪弄来的那东西
Where did you get that?
他是谁
Who's he?
这是弗兰克
This is Frank.
- 谢谢你帮忙  - 不客气
- Thanks for your help. - Thanks.
我以为你接受了那笔交易
I thought you were taking the deal.
我意识到这可能会使父权制永远延续下去
I realized it would be perpetuating the patriarchy.
总有人会告诉女人
There's always someone telling women
她们的存在只有一个原因
they only exist for one reason.
我们甚至也是这么告诉自己的
We even told it to ourselves.
我不想再这样了
I am done playing that game.
该终结游戏了
Screw endgame.
你找到了另一种出路
You've... found another way.
你杀了人身牛头怪
You killed the Minotaur.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你不该承受那种生活
Not that you deserved it.
当然这种生活你也配不上
And you definitely don't deserve this.
这一天真的受够了女人不停地为难女人
We've had enough of women hurting other women for one day.
错误的解药像卡在喉咙里的骨头
* When the wrong antidote is like a bone in the throat *
One Thing Leads to Another - THE FIXX
他们这么谨慎地寻找掩护  为什么他们
* They run for cover so discreet, why don't they *
不按他们说的去做
* Do what they say *
心口如一
* Say what you mean *
宝贝  一件事引发另一件
* Baby, one thing leads to another *
你跟我说不对劲
* You told me something wrong *
我知道我听得太多  不过
* I know I listen too long, but then *
一件事总是由另一件引起的
* One thing leads to another. *
Take on Me - WENDY WANG, INGA ROBERTS
我们谈过了
* We're talking away *
我不知是什么缘由
* I don't know what *
我说
* I'm to say *
我还是要说
* I'll say it anyway *
今天来见你
* Today isn't my day *
我绝对
* To find you *
不该回避
* Shying away *
我会为你的爱而来  明白吗
* I'll be coming for your love, okay? *
接
* Take *
纳
* On *
我
* Me *
* I'll *
会
* Be *
离开
* Gone... *
想不想去别的地方跳舞
Do you maybe want to dance somewhere else?
该不会在暗示什么吧
Only if that's a metaphor.
接纳我
* Take on me *
* Take me on *
在今天
* In a day... *
- 快点  我们还能阻止他们  - 等等
- Hurry, we can still stop them. - Wait.
为什么
For what?
让他们去吧
We have to let them go.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
接纳我
* Take on me. *
咒语
Motus.
这衣服连袖子都没有
This doesn't even have sleeves.
怎么
Why is this
这么难脱
so hard to take off?
你确定要这么做吗
You sure you want to do this?
我这辈子从来没这么肯定过
I've never been so sure of anything in my life.
你有避孕套吗
Do you have a condom?
我就知道我肯定忘了什么
I knew I forgot something.
不  别动  别动
Don't-- stop, stop.
别动
Do not move.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
I Melt with You - MODERN ENGLISH
所有的好人都到哪里去了
* Where have all the good men gone *
- 该死  - 诸神又去了哪里
- Damn it. - * And where are all the gods? *
街头的大力神去了哪里
* Where's the streetwise Hercules *
为了增加胜算吗
* To fight the rising odds? *
难道没有白衣骑士吗
* Isn't there a white knight *
骑着烈马飞驰
* Upon a fiery steed? *
韦德
Wade!
我辗转反侧
* I toss and I turn*
算了
Never mind.
无所谓
Whatever.
那么  你叫韦德是吗
So, your name's Wade, then?
一般大家都会叫错
Usually nobody gets it right.
你是谁
Who are you?
你需要  比如  一个相机
Do you need, like, a camera
或者什么东西来参加聚会吗
or something for the party?
不  不  不
No. No, no, no.
韦德  我需要的是
What I need, Wade, is...
一个朋友
a friend.
我要使世界停止转动  和你一起享受感动
* I'll stop the world and melt with you *
你看过
* You've seen... *
我不明白
I don't get it.
我们为了回到这里简直是自杀
We literally killed ourselves to get back here,
你坚持不下去
and you couldn't go through with it.
你之前说的
What you said before,
关于命运
about destiny,
你是对的
you were right.
他和乔西在一起看起来很幸福
You know, he and Josie, they look happy together.
不是每件事都只有一种可能
Maybe there isn't only one way everything has to happen.
我们不是为了一种情况而存在
We don't exist for just one path.
我们不是为了一个男孩而存在
And we don't exist for just one boy.
让我们跳舞
So let's dance.
做点事不让我去想
Anything to keep me from picturing
乔西和夏尔的不幸爱恋
Josie's tragic visit to the Shire.
我要使世界停止转动  和你一起享受感动
* I'll stop the world and melt with you *
如果你告诉别人
If you tell this to anyone,
我不会承认的
I will deny it.
但我很高兴你回来了
But I'm glad to have you back.
我们在一起  没有什么做不到
* There's nothing you and I won't do*
我要使世界停止转动
* I'll stop the world*
和你一起享受感动
* And melt with you *
我要使世界停止转动  和你一起享受感动
* I'll stop the world and melt with you *
Holding Out For A Hero - BONNIE TYLER
我要使世界停止转动
* I'll stop the world *
和你一起享受感动
* And melt with you *
我要使世界停止转动  和你一起享受感动
* I'll stop the world and melt with you. *
威廉先生
Mr. Williams,
抱歉打扰了
sorry to interrupt.
- 没事  兰登  - 你还记得
- All good, Landon. - Do you remember
我们之前谈过什么吗
what we talked about earlier?
你是对的
You were right.
那么  兄弟  你还在这干什么
Then, boy, what the hell are you doing here?
向你借车钥匙
Uh, asking to borrow your car keys.
因为我得快点
'Cause I need to make a quick--
飞快地冲进城
a real quick-- run into town.
冲进城里吗
Run into town?
在这种情况下
In that case,
你不想要我的车钥匙
you don't want my car keys.
你想要护士办公室的钥匙
You want the keys to the nurse's office.
你会在她的桌子里找到你要找的东西
You'll find what you're looking for in her desk.
他沉稳自信  当机立断
* He's gotta be sure and it's gotta be soon *
谢谢
* And he's gotta be larger * Thank you.
顶天立地
* Than life *
渴望一位英雄
* I need a hero *
我痴痴的等待  直至长夜渐尽
* I'm holding out for a hero till the end of the night *
不
No.
现在不行  你们这些蠢老鼠
Not now, you stupid rats.
我一直在听你那老鼠爪子的声音
I have been listening to your tiny little rat claws
好几个月了
for months now...
火焰
亲爱的日记
我80年代的服装糟透了
没人知道我打扮成了外星人
一首关于希望的歌
作者兰登·柯比
向我的小朋友问好
Say hello to my little friend.
我想这样会更好
* Well, I guess it'd be nice... *
嘿
Hey. Um...
还好吗
is everything okay?
如果我告诉你我想再等等  你会生气吗
would you be mad if I told you that I wanted to wait?
但我得三思而后行
* But I gotta think twice... *
不
No.
- 不会的  - 我很抱歉
- Not at all. - I'm sorry.
- 我只是  - 没事的
- I just, um... - It doesn't matter.
不管怎样
Whatever it is,
如果你还没准备好  我也没准备好
if you're not ready for it, neither am I.
我们有的是时间  乔西
We have all the time in the world, Josie.
从那种情绪
* From that emotion *
什么都改变不了这一点
Nothing's gonna change that.
是时候把我的心从地板上捡起来了
* Time to pick my heart up off the floor *
当爱降临的时候
* And when that love comes down *
没有奉献
* Without devotion *
嗯  这需要
* Well, it takes... *
你想喝杯茶吗
You want a cup of tea?
恩
Yeah.
好
Okay.
Faith - SLEEPING AT LAST
因为我必须要有信念
* 'Cause I got to have faith *
我必须要有信念
* I got to have faith *
* I got to have faith, faith *
噢  宝贝  我重新考虑了
* Oh, baby, I reconsider *
我愚蠢的想法
* My foolish notion *
我需要有人来抱着我
* Well, I need someone to hold me *
但我会等待更多的事情发生
* But I'll wait for something more *
我必须要有信念
* I got to have faith. *
嘿
Hey!
* Hey! *
霍普
Hope?
嘿  拉斐尔
Hey, Raf.
我刚想着今晚能见到你
I was hoping to see you tonight.
你
Do you...
想和我们一起聚会吗
want to party with us?
我喜欢你的什么地方
* What I like about you *
What I Like About You - LILLIX
当然
Sure.
女巫们有点醉了
The witches are a little drunk.
你意识到了
You do realize
你上的是最蠢的学校  对吧
you go to the dopest school of all time, right?
你应该告诉
You should probably tell that
你后面那个穿黑外套的家伙
to the dude behind you in the black coat.
你在说谁
Who are you talking about?
盯着你的那个
The one staring at you.
这就是我喜欢你的地方
* That's what I like about you. *
我已经没有多少朋友可以聊天了
* I ain't got many friends left to talk to *
遇到麻烦的时候无处可逃
* Nowhere to run when I'm in trouble... *
我得说  我很惊讶
I must say, I'm surprised.
你是我最没想到
You're the last person I expected
会请我喝酒的人
to invite me for a drink.
坐吧
Have a seat.
我只是想用你的爱
* I just want to use your love... *
Your Love - THE OUTFIELD
我为你点了一杯带小伞装饰的酒
I ordered you something with an umbrella.
我不想失去你的爱
* I don't want to lose your love... *
听着
Look,
我希望学校成功
I want the school to succeed,
这意味着你必须成功
which means you have to succeed.
所以拜托
So, please,
请比我强
be better than I was.
这是一个很低的标准
That's a very low bar.
这就是你打我脸的方式吗
Is this the part where you punch me in the face?
只在我的脑海里出现过
Only in my mind.
摇晃着
* From shaking *
但有些事在我心里
* But something in my mind's... *
我不会挡你的路
I'll stay out of your way.
但记住
But remember...
你要对我爱的人负责
...you're responsible for people I love.
当你离开的时候  请把门关上好吗
* As you're leaving, please, would you close the door? *
我要为此干杯
I'll drink to that.
别忘了我对你说过的话
* Don't forget what I told you *
只是因为你是对的
* Just 'cause you're right... *
是的
Yes, please.
泪流满面
* To cry upon *
我只是想拥有你的爱
* I just want to use your love *
今晚
* Tonight *
是的
* Yeah *
我不想失去你的爱
* I don't want to lose your love *
今晚
* Tonight *
是的
* Yeah *
今晚我只想拥有你的爱
* I just want to use your love tonight... *
你是从哪里来的
Where did you come from?
我一直都在这里
Oh, I've been here the whole time.
我很抱歉  我无意冒犯
I'm sorry. I don't mean to be forward,
但我熟悉你的味道
but I know your smell.
好吧
Uh, okay.
真的很臭
It's a stench, really,
像垃圾站
a pit.
马里之洼
Malivore.
你怎么知道这个名字的
How do you know that name?
说来话长
Ah, it's a long story.
或许我带你看看可能会更好
Probably better if I just show you.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）